# DERIS HARDIANSYAH ISMAIL

Bogor, Jawa Barat 16963 | +62 81311876610 | derishardiansyah27@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a recent graduate with programming and database management experience, I have worked on diverse projects. My love for technology and continuous learning drives my career. I am proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, and have optimised databases for performance and data security. I am committed to keeping up to date with industry trends and welcome future challenges and opportunities.

## **SKILLS**

- Front-End Skills: HTML, CSS, SCSS
- Scripting Languages: PHP, Python, JavaScript
  Graphic and User Interface Design
- · Database Skills: SQL
- Network Installation, Maintenance and Repair
- Data Modeling
- · Communication and Interpersonal Skills
- Teamwork and Collaboration

## **EXPERIENCE**

07/2023 - 09/2023

#### Full Stack Developer Trainee

PT. PhinCon - Tebet, Jakarta Selatan, Indonesia

- Developed a feature-rich 2023-2024 premier league football club information system application
- Frontend stack includes React JS and Redux Saga for state management, coupled with Material-UI for polished UI components
- Customised styling is achieved through SCSS, ensuring a modern look and feel to the app
- Backend infrastructure built on Express.js, implements JWT for secure authentication
- · Sequelize integrated as database middleware, providing efficient ORM capabilities for data management
- Cloudinary is integrated for seamless media upload, enhancing user experience and as an online data repository
- Utilised Redis and MySQL for efficient data management and improved performance

## 08/2021 - 10/2021

#### Web Developer - Intern

Direktorat Perencanaan Kawasan Konservasi (Ditjen KSDAE - Kementerian Lingkungan Hidup dan Kehutanan) - Bogor, Jawa Barat, Indonesia

- Building a website-based geographic information system
- Used GIS technology, equipment or systems to produce data layers, maps, tables and reports
- · Collected, created, edited and processed spatial data to support geographic information system
- Make mapping for integrated management units and institutions in conservation areas

## 10/2020 - 10/2020

## Software Developer

Kementerian Pendidikan dan Kebudayaan (Ministry of Education and Culture Republic of **Indonesia**) - Indonesia

 Interface software designed to be user-friendly for tracking and various information related to covid-19

#### 01/2017 - 03/2017

#### Network Engineer - Intern

PT. Permata Sejahtra Buana - Bogor, Jawa Barat, Indonesia

- Optimized, enhanced and expanded network capabilities and connectivity through network monitoring tools
- Perform scheduled maintenance without service interruption
- · Perform configure network equipment for installation, perform a refresh and perform post-installation testing

# **EDUCATION**

09/2018 - 01/2023

**Bachelor of Computer:** Computer Science **Universitas Pakuan**- Bogor, Indonesia Grade: 3,75 out of 4,00 (Very Satisfy)

# **LANGUAGES**

Indonesia: First Language

English: A2

Elementary

# **ORGANIZATION**

- Member, Himpunan Mahasiswa Ilmu Komputer (HIMAKOM) (2019 2023)
- Member, Forum Komunikasi Mahasiswa Islam (FKMI) (2019)